Guide to the Football Programs Collection, 1891 - 2005
Football Programs Collection, 1891 - 2005
Special Collections & Archives, Wesleyan University
Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)
1000-46
1.25
3
The Wesleyan football team has been in existence since 1883.
The Football Programs Collection contains programs for Wesleyan home and away games from 1891 through 2005. The collection is not complete for all years.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisitions Information
Assembled by the Wesleyan University Archives
Accrual Information
Regular additions to this collection are expected.
Historical Note
The Wesleyan football team has been in existence since 1883.
Collection Overview
The Football Programs Collection contains programs for Wesleyan home and away games from 1891 through 2005. The collection is not complete for all years.
Collection Arrangement
The programs are arranged in chronological order.
Online Catalog Headings
These and related materials may be found under the following headings in online catalogs.
Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.) --Football.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.) --Sports.; Athletics--Connecticut--Middletown--20th century.; Athletics--Connecticut--Middletown--19th century.; College sports.
Related Material
Athletic Teams’ Records, Wesleyan University Special Collections & Archives
Detailed Description of the Collection
  - November 3, 1891, at Harvard (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Note: Score card only.
  - November 24, 1892, at Penn
  - October 9, 1894, Amherst
  - November 14, 1903, Williams (Folder 2)
  - October 29, 1904, Dartmouth
  - November 11, 1905, Williams
  - November 9, 1907, Williams
  - November 7, 1908, Trinity
  - November 6, 1909, Williams
  - September 28, 1910, at Yale
  - October 8, 1910, Amherst
  - October 15, 1910, Norwich
  - October 29, 1910, Trinity
  - November 5, 1910, at Williams
  - November 12, 1910, NYU
  - November 9, 1912, at Williams (Folder 3)
  - November 16, 1912, Trinity
    Note: Includes official game souvenir.
  - October 25, 1913, Amherst
  - November 8, 1913, Williams
  - November 15, 1913, at NYU
  - November 7, 1914, at Willliams
  - November 14, 1914, Trinity
  - 1915 Columbia season program
  - November 6, 1915, Williams
  - November 1, 1919, Williams
  - November 19, 1921, Williams (Folder 4)
  - October 18, 1924, Amherst
  - October 31, 1925, Trinity
  - September 29, 1928, Bates
  - October 20, 1928, Rochester
  - November 2, 1929, Trinity
  - November 9, 1929, Williams
  - October 10, 1931, Columbia (Folder 5)
  - September 30, 1933, Union
  - November 11, 1933, Williams
  - November 10, 1934, at Williams
  - October 26, 1935, at Amherst
  - October 31, 1936, Trinity
  - November 7, 1936, at Williams
  - October 16, 1937, Haverford
  - October 30, 1937, at Trinity
  - October 22, 1938, Amherst
  - October 29, 1938, Trinity
  - November 5, 1938, at Williams
  - September 30, 1939, at Rutgers
  - October 7, 1939, UConn
  - November 4, 1939, Coast Guard
  - November 11, 1939, Williams
  - November 18, 1939, at Trinity
  - October 26, 1940, Amherst
  - November 16, 1940, Trinity
  - October 18, 1941, Haverford (Folder 6)
  - October 11, 1941, University of Connecticut
  - October 25, 1941, at Amherst
  - November 1, 1941, Coast Guard
  - November 8, 1941, Williams
  - November 15, 1941, at Trinity
  - December 29, 1941, at Rutgers
  - October 10, 1942, at University of Connecticut
  - October 17, 1942, Swarthmore
  - October 24, 1942, Amherst
  - November 14, 1942, Trinity
  - October 6, 1945, at W.P.I.
  - October 12, 1946, University of Connecticut (Folder 7)
  - October 18, 1946, at Middlebury
  - October 26, 1946, Amherst
  - November 2, 1946, Haverford
  - November 9, 1946, at Williams
  - November 16, 1946, Trinity
  - October 4, 1947, W.P.I.
  - October 11, 1947, at University of Connecticut
  - October 18, 1947, Swarthmore
  - October 25, 1947, at Amherst
  - November 1, 1947, at Haverford
  - November 8, 1947, Williams
  - November 15, 1947, at Trinity
  - October 9, 1948, at Coast Guard
  - October 16, 1948, at Swarthmore
  - October 23, 1948, Amherst
  - November 12, 1949, at Trinity
  - September 29, 1951, Middlebury (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - November 7, 1953, Williams
  - September 25, 1954, at Middlebury
  - October 2, 1954, at Tufts
  - October 8, 1955, Coast Guard
  - October 22, 1955, at Amherst
  - October 13, 1956, Haverford
  - September 28, 1957, Middlebury
  - November 15, 1958, Trinity
  - September 26, 1959, Middlebury
  - October 10, 1959, Coast Guard
  - November 7, 1959, Williams
  - October 8, 1960, at Coast Guard
  - November 5, 1960, at Williams
  - September 30, 1961, Middlebury (Folder 2)
  - October 21, 1961, at W.P.I.
  - September 28, 1963, Middlebury
  - October 5, 1963, at Bowdoin
  - October 12, 1963, Coast Guard
  - November 2, 1963, Hamilton
  - November 9, 1963, Williams
  - October 3, 1964, Bowdoin
  - October 24, 1964, Amherst
  - November 14, 1964, Trinity
  - September 25, 1965, Middlebury
  - October 30, 1965 Hamilton
  - November 6, 1965, Williams
  - November 13, 1965, at Trinity
  - October 1, 1966, Bowdoin (Folder 3)
  - October 22, 1966, Amherst
  - November 12, 1966, Trinity
  - October 14, 1967, Coast Guard
  - October 21, 1967, at W.P.I.
  - October 28, 1967, at Amherst
  - November 11, 1967, Williams
  - October 5, 1968, Bowdoin
  - October 12, 1968, at Coast Guard
  - October 19, 1968, W.P.I.
  - October 26, 1968, Amherst
  - November 2, 1968, at Hamilton
  - November 9, 1968, at Williams
  - November 16, 1968, Trinity
  - November 1, 1969, Hamilton (Folder 4)
  - November 8, 1969, Williams
  - October 10, 1970, at Coast Guard
  - October 17, 1970, W.P.I.
  - October 24, 1970, Amherst
  - November 14, 1970, Trinity
  - September 25, 1971, Middlebury
  - October 9, 1971, Coast Guard
  - October 23, 1971, at Amherst
  - October 30, 1971, Hamilton
  - November 6, 1971, Williams
  - October 7, 1972, Bowdoin (Folder 5)
  - October 21, 1972, W.P.I.
  - October 28, 1972, Amherst
  - November 18, 1972, Trinity
  - September 22, 1973, Southern Connecticut
  - September 29, 1973, Middlebury
  - October 13, 1973, Coast Guard
  - November 10, 1973, Williams
  - September 28, 1974, at Middlebury
  - October 5, 1974, Bowdoin
  - October 19, 1974, W.P.I.
  - October 26, 1974, Amherst
  - November 16, 1974, Trinity
  - September 20, 1975, Southern Connecticut (Folder 6)
  - September 27, 1975, Middlebury
  - October 11, 1975, Coast Guard
  - November 8, 1975, Williams
  - November 15, 1975, at Trinity
  - October 9, 1976, at Coast Guard
  - November 7, 1981, Williams (Folder 7)
  - October 25, 1986, at Bowdoin
  - September 28, 1996, Hamilton (Folder 8)
  - October 31, 1998, Bowdoin
  - October 21, 2000, Amherst
  - October 28, 2000, Bowdoin
  - November 3, 2001, Williams (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - October 19, 2002, Amherst
  - September 20, 2003, Middlebury
  - November 1, 2003, Williams
  - October 23, 2004, Amherst
  - November 13, 2004, Trinity
  - September 24, 2005, Tufts (Folder 2)
  - October 8, 2005, Colby
  - October 15, 2005, Bates
  - October 22, 2005, Amherst
  - November 5, 2005, Williams
  - September 30, 2006, Hamilton (Folder 3)